Hello Hello Friends, in this video I am going to
talk to you about this bank
and Yes Bank, so we will first look at this issue,
subscribe and
apart from this we will talk in this way,
this time let's subscribe
and we will talk about them, first of all,
he subscribed to this bank
and
in the watch section, the
5% upper circuit in the share price of Yes Bank
was a testimony to the fact that the
credit rating of Yes Bank has
improved, somewhere or the other,
subscribe to it, subscribe here that it is
a positive sentiment and subscribe
that in Bigg Boss, innovativeness has been
improved in that,
in the infrastructure bond program, its triple A rating
towards Bulb School, which they also subscribe in
this way, subscribe, subscribe
and after that the next news was that if you have
upgraded them, Ikraar upgraded
Reliance, listen to them carefully,
first they told that they had done
capital race, like subscribe and
means that due to which the bank
Subscribe to the channel. Share capital is called
Tier 1 capital. If I explain it to you in simple language,
it is permanent capital. The
capital which will never go out of the bank is
called Tier 1 capital.
The givers in it are better than the bank and that
too should improve. So ultimately, the
appointed subscriber here. On the other hand, he
said that because of this, there has been a lot of improvement
and subscribe. Apart from this, the accused who have
sunk the deposits here, subscribe subscribe, in this way, are working tirelessly to
repack the deposits and they have
achieved success to a great extent in this and the main
result of this was that the management repaired the liquid of
Rs 50 thousand crore and said that it will be given to
them.
During this period, Shukra was appointed subscriber, so
you can subscribe with the help of this
and subscribe. The
second marriage was done through Permanent Capital which is
through SBI. The bank had sunk
and SBI had requested many other
banks to put money here.
They also put in a lot of money. The
person who had put in a lot of money is who is
The capital of two tier one capital will
never be repaired by merging it with the capital, but the
money that the person had
in the form of loan has been repaired, so
this repacking of Rs 50,000 is a
positive step for Yes Bank. After that,
see, this festival subscribed money was
lent there, now there is subscription to school and ghee ki
yudh, due to which
Bigg Boss, because you will
write that the person who is coming to deposit on your account, the
customer who is coming, the investor who is
coming, puts some money in it on this condition that
I get some extra views, so
look at it this way, let's also
see it like it was about the channel bank, the
rate of interest they are giving you on the central deposit, in
this way you will
see the difference of deposits, and on the other hand,
using this technique, this brinjal is
attracting more and more customers,
so because of that, the number of deposits is
increasing, due to which there can be
no problem in recovery, the collection which
is still here  But
what prevents me from doing that in cancer? The
liability side has been managed by
setting up the liability, which means that the capital,
Tier 1 capital, Tier 2 capital has been romanced.
Their rating agencies have been given a restating
lemon. Money has started coming from customers, which means that the
deposits have started
coming in and deposits have started increasing again.
But the problem is that there is
still improvement on the recovery front from the asset side. When there was a
printhead improvement in recovery, you will see it
in the future. So see, its texture is
positive even in their poster last.
And secondly, it will be visible inside their balance sheet
and most importantly,
you will see a direct impact on their share price also. So
see, the
liability setup has been romanced. Now it
is the turn of the upset side. Now we hope
that in the next three to six months, the
recovery process through this side will be quite good. Even the
hatred is not at that level that
we can say that we have reached the subscribed level.
After that, one and a half price moment this week.
So in this ancient age, if you
say, the Yes Bank stock has closed above the highest level of the week. So, the highest
closing of the last 15 days was
given by Yes Bank, so there is
no tightness in it, it has not deteriorated,
people will increase and Rashmi, it has given you Prakash
improvement, although Bank
Nifty is associated with negative bias,
but if we
talk about this subscription, then subscribe to the iron appointment on it,
so subscribe there, there will be a
good closing on Monday,
now see, or if we
talk about its price, then
definitely subscribe on Monday,
looking at the next day of Uttar Pradesh, the
channel
remained in the 13-train while doing 65 on Paise Police, but after that, in
Thursday and Friday, April
closed at the price of 1365 to 1314, if you see, the delivery volume was the
highest on 40, which is
within three days and if you  Talking about Wednesday,
it was not subscribed on 40th
and if you had subscribed then
subscribe it completely, do
not forget to subscribe to the channel, it is doing
100 feet, so Yasmin is
also not untouched by it and this because it is the
route shown earlier old photo, it will take
some time from there but at least for you,
subscription is first important for them, so along with this,
you should
definitely subscribe, how did you like this video,
thank you.